<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Joon Career</title><link>https://jooncode.com/</link><description>Recent content on Joon Career</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jooncode.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design Patterns</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blogs/class/ood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blogs/class/ood/</guid><description>Introduction Design patterns are essential in development as they provide a structured approach to solve common problems. Object-oriented design patterns are the most widely used patterns, and they form the backbone of most software applications. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my experience as a OOD TA and insights on how these patterns work and provide you with some sample code to help you understand them better. We will explore Singleton, Factory, Strategy, and Observer patterns, and how these patterns can be used to improve the quality of your designs and provide you with code samples to illustrate their implementation.</description></item><item><title>My 2022: Coming back from military!</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blogs/gallery/2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blogs/gallery/2022/</guid><description/></item><item><title>AI League of Legend</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blogs/game/leagueaibot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blogs/game/leagueaibot/</guid><description>What if there is Faker Bot in League? As a computer science student, I find artificial intelligence (AI) bots fascinating. I want to extend the AI idea within the context of popular video games. With the development of AI technology, the way we play video games has drastically changed. AI-powered video games are now more interactive and immersive than ever before and have opened up a world of possibilities for gamers.</description></item><item><title>Discord Bot Development story</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blogs/class/nestdiscordbot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blogs/class/nestdiscordbot/</guid><description>Introduction Software engineering is a rapidly changing field. Every day, new tools and technologies are being released that can help developers more efficiently create and manage applications. As a software engineer, it can be difficult to keep up with all the changes and ensure that you are staying up to date with the latest best practices. In this blog post, I will share my experience reaching out to my favorite league data analysis youtuber&amp;rsquo;s company and apply my knowlege and skill out side of class.</description></item></channel></rss>