<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Joon Career</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Joon Career</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jooncode.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Irreplaceable Developer</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/to-be-good-developer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/to-be-good-developer/</guid><description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced technological landscape, the role of a software developer is undergoing a rapid shift. The traditional responsibility of coding, debugging, and deployment are now just the baseline knowledge.The rise of AI-assisted tools like GitHub Copilot and language models like ChatGPT has accelerated this change, streamlining the coding process and enhancing code quality.
As a result, being a successful developer today necessitates not only coding skills but also a deep understanding of client needs and creative problem-solving that extends beyond code.</description></item><item><title>Enhanced Valorant Metrics</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/enhancedmetrics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/enhancedmetrics/</guid><description>Agent-Based Rating In combat score systems, metrics such as damage per point, kill points based on remaining enemies, multi-kills, and assists offer a general overview of players’ combat effectiveness. However, this approach overlooks the nuanced roles and abilities of different agents like Raze, Jett, and Reyna, who may excel in specific conditions that disproportionately inflate their combat scores. Ranking players solely on these scores would neither be equitable nor accurately represent their contributions to team victories.</description></item><item><title>Backend System Design</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/backend/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/backend/</guid><description>Building the backend infrastructure for our Valorant data-driven website, I encountered several unique challenges and oppurtunities to grow as a software developer. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll outline our current implementations and the ongoing developments for our backend system design.
Pipeline with Kafka In our quest to build an advanced and reliable infrastructure, Kafka became a cornerstone of our design. The integration effectively separates our crawler from our statistical calculation components, aiming for a system that remains robust, especially when it faces potential computational challenges.</description></item><item><title>Crafting the Main Page</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/mainpage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/mainpage/</guid><description>Understanding Valorant Valorant&amp;rsquo;s unique appeal is rooted in its foundational design philosophy that promotes a layered gaming experience. Players are incentivized when they successfully gather information, strategize their moves, and execute these strategies. This progression is termed the &amp;ldquo;tactical cycle,&amp;rdquo; and following it often leads to victories. The developers have thoughtfully crafted both maps and agents to further reinforce this cycle.
Each agent possesses distinct strengths and vulnerabilities that can deeply influence gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Valorant Website Project</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/introduction/</guid><description>My Experience with Riot For the past 10 years, Riot Games has been the cornerstone of my gaming experience. I&amp;rsquo;ve always enjoyed those competitive moments, playing alongside friends to clutch those hard-earned victories in League of Legends and Valorant.
I was enthusiastic enough to want more friends to join my lobby. Yet, the highly competitive nature of Riot games made it challenging for me as an advanced player to guide them.</description></item><item><title>Building a Match Crawler</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/crawler/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/crawler/</guid><description>Before I check my insights of Valorant with stats, the foremost task was to construct a robust data crawler. This pivotal first step would act as the foundation, paving the way for any meaningful analysis. When building a data crawler to fetch, process, and store a massive amount of data, challenges are inevitable. As I embarked on my journey to create a crawler for Valorant&amp;rsquo;s match data, I encountered a series of obstacles that pushed me to optimize my approach in terms of speed, storage, and robustness.</description></item><item><title>Agent difficulty Paradox</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/agentparadox/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/agentparadox/</guid><description>The realm of Valorant offers players numerous agents, each boasting unique abilities and strategies to win. But how do players, both new and experienced, navigate this vast selection?
With a combination of Python programming and a rich dataset extracted from MongoDB, I obtained the performance metrics of various agents across different skill tiers. The result challenges widely held beliefs and shed light on the actual efficacy of agents in various gameplay scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Design Patterns</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/ood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/ood/</guid><description>Design patterns are essential in development as they provide a structured approach to solve common problems. Object-oriented design patterns are the most widely used patterns, and they form the backbone of most software applications.
In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my experience as a OOD TA and insights on how these patterns work and provide you with some sample code to help you understand them better. We will explore Singleton, Factory, Strategy, and Observer patterns, and how these patterns can be used to improve the quality of your designs and provide you with code samples to illustrate their implementation.</description></item><item><title>My first custom keyboard</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/keyboard/frogtkl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/keyboard/frogtkl/</guid><description>Nothing crazy. Just some typing video with my first custom keyboard.</description></item><item><title>My 2022: Coming back from military!</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/gallery/2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/gallery/2022/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Discord Bot Development story</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/nestdiscordbot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/code/nestdiscordbot/</guid><description>Software engineering is a rapidly changing field. Every day, new tools and technologies are being released that can help developers more efficiently create and manage applications. As a software engineer, it can be difficult to keep up with all the changes and ensure that you are staying up to date with the latest best practices. In this blog post, I will share my experience reaching out to my favorite league data analysis youtuber&amp;rsquo;s company and apply my knowlege and skill out side of class.</description></item><item><title>AI League of Legend</title><link>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/leagueaibot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jooncode.com/blog/game/leagueaibot/</guid><description>What if there is Faker Bot in League? As a computer science student, I find artificial intelligence (AI) bots fascinating. I want to extend the AI idea within the context of popular video games. With the development of AI technology, the way we play video games has drastically changed. AI-powered video games are now more interactive and immersive than ever before and have opened up a world of possibilities for gamers.</description></item></channel></rss>